<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>geekyboy88</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on geekyboy88</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year Chinese Chess</title>
      <link>/post/chinese-new-year-chinese-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/chinese-new-year-chinese-chess/</guid>
      <description>body, td { font-size: 18px; } code.r{ font-size: 18px; } pre { font-size: 18px }  Chinese New Year Chinese Chess? Hi again! As of the time of this post, we are fast approaching the month of February. What awaits us in February is a long holiday which some of us folks will celebrate, Chinese New Year!! So in light of the coming festivities, I thought I could do something (related to) Chinese, but not so much the New Year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer and Discipline - Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/soccer-and-discipline-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/soccer-and-discipline-part-2/</guid>
      <description>body, td { font-size: 18px; } code.r{ font-size: 18px; } pre { font-size: 18px }  Soccer and Discipline - Part 2 In my previous post, I approached soccer analytics from the discipline perspective, and tried to estimate what the probability of getting a yellow card is, on the condition that the referee calls it a foul in the first place.
To provide another perspective, this time round, I wanted to dig further to discover what other insights about disciplinary issues we can glean from the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer and Discipline</title>
      <link>/post/soccer-and-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/soccer-and-discipline/</guid>
      <description>body, td { font-size: 18px; } code.r{ font-size: 18px; } pre { font-size: 18px }  Soccer and Discipline Hi everyone again. For my third post, I have decided to look at some soccer data that was recently uploaded at Kaggle. This is a mega dataset comprising close to 900k records of events across a number of major European leagues over the course of about 5 seasons. The great thing about events data is that it gives you a really intricate flavour of what happens in the match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Parking Time!</title>
      <link>/post/2018-01-08-it-s-parking-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/2018-01-08-it-s-parking-time/</guid>
      <description>body, td { font-size: 18px; } code.r{ font-size: 18px; } pre { font-size: 18px }  Open Data in Singapore Hi again! For my second post, I would like to focus on exploring the open data sources available at data.gov.sg. But should one click on the link that I just provided and take a look at the available data sources, one would find an immense number of data sets available, and wouldn’t necessarily know where to begin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Duty Calls</title>
      <link>/post/when-duty-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/when-duty-calls/</guid>
      <description>body, td { font-size: 18px; } code.r{ font-size: 18px; } pre { font-size: 18px }  My first official post Alright. I realised that my first post wasn’t supposed to be online, so I had to remove it for good reasons. Anyhow, I’m still keen on getting my first official data science post up, so here we go!
 Mediacorp Channel 8 Prime Time To start off, I need to introduce some facts about myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/post/2017-12-19-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/post/2017-12-19-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, this is my first blog post here.
I enjoy working on data, and will be starting to post some of my work here.
Hope you will find this interesting! :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About myself</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>kennethang7@gmail.com (Kenneth)</author>
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Kenneth, and I am a Singaporean who really loves working with data. I&amp;rsquo;m starting this blog to share some of stuff that I have done in the data space!
Cheers!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>